scnet.net 2014-08-31

# Privacy Policy | ServerCentral

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy describes how the personal information you may provide to us via this website is collected, processed, and used. Any personal information you provide us will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The following policy is only in effect with regard to the website located at _www.servercentral.com_ (the “ **Site** ”), which is owned and operated by ServerCentral (“ **ServerCentral** ”). This policy may be revised from time to time, so please revisit this page often to remain fully informed of our policies.

**Does ServerCentral adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles?**

ServerCentral complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland (“PII” as defined below). ServerCentral has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement (the “Principles”). To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view ServerCentral’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the practices for implementing the Principles, the Principles shall govern. This Privacy Policy outlines our general policy and practices for implementing the Principles, including the types of information we gather, how we use it and the notice and choice affected individuals have regarding our use and their ability to correct that information.  This Privacy Policy applies to all personal information received by the company whether in electronic, paper, or verbal format.

**How does ServerCentral handle requests to view, remove or modify personally identifiable information?**

ServerCentral defines personally identifiable information” (“ **PII** ”) as information that identifies, or can identify you as an individual, such as a residential address, telephone number, or billing information, and defines non-personally identifiable information” (“ **Non-PII”** ) as aggregated information, demographic data, IP addresses, and other information that does not reveal your specific identity.

When you visit and interact with this Site, ServerCentral and third parties with whom ServerCentral contracts to provide services to ServerCentral may collect Non-PII (for example, a catalog of the Site pages you visit). Non-PII is anonymous and does not identify you personally.

If you have completed our “Contact Us” or “Request a Quote” forms and would like to ask ServerCentral to stop using PII provided at that time, please contact us at [privacy@servercentral.com](mailto:privacy@servercentral.com). Please note, however, that while we will honor your request to stop using your PII, we may need to retain a record of your PII to comply with applicable federal, state or local law.

In addition, we strive to maintain the accuracy of any PII that may be collected from you, and will use our commercially reasonable efforts to respond promptly to update our database when you tell us the information in our database is not accurate. If you are a customer, you can view and change your registration PII, customer preferences, and profile information by emailing our finance department at [ar@servercentral.com](mailto:ar@servercentral.com), or by logging into our customer portal. It is your responsibility to ensure that such information is accurate, complete and up-to-date.

If you would like to communicate with us about this Privacy Policy or ServerCentral’s collection and use of your PII, please use the Contact Us form on our Site or email us at [privacy@servercentral.com](mailto:privacy@servercentral.com) _._

**What technical information is ServerCentral collecting and how is it collecting it?**

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, which serve as that computer’s “Internet Protocol” or IP address. When a visitor requests a page from the Site, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor’s domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our Site.

Our Web servers also collect information about the type of Internet browser you are using, operating system, as well as which of the Site’s pages you have accessed. This information is used to help our team develop Web pages that display properly for the majority of our visitors. Our Web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of its visitors.

**Does ServerCentral use cookies?**

Yes, ServerCentral uses cookies. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are often used to provide you with a customized experience. At no time is any personal information stored within any ServerCentral created or provided cookie. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but it is possible to change your browser setup so that it does not accept cookies. Accepting cookies through your browser is a personal choice. You can still enjoy ServerCentral’s Site if you choose not to accept cookies.

**What personally identifiable information does ServerCentral collect when I complete the “Contact Us” and “Request a Quote” forms?**

Whenever you send us an e-mail via the Contact Us form on the Site, you may be providing us with your first name, last name, email address, company name and any additional information you choose to provide in the text of your message. For example, you may choose to provide your phone number, mailing address or other information necessary or helpful for us to address your query or concern. Any information supplied by you through our Contact Us form is used to aid our business to respond to your request and provide you with the necessary information.

Additionally, the Site permits you to reach out to us to request a quote regarding our products and services via our Request a Quote form. When you request a quote through the Site, you may be providing us with your first name, last name, phone number, email address, and any additional information you choose to provide in the comments section of the Request a Quote form (e.g., your address and/or any additional information regarding your request).

_When you provide us your e-mail address via the Contact Us or Request a Quote forms, you will not automatically be subscribed to any regular electronic communications from ServerCentral._

**Does ServerCentral track, or allow third parties to track, online activity?**

We do not engage in the collection of personally identifiable information about your online activities over time or across third party websites or online services. Accordingly, we do not currently process or comply with any web browser’s “do not track” signal or other third party mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information. However, to the extent a third party link or advertisement displayed on the Site contains third party cookies, such cookies may enable such third party to collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and/or across different websites.

**How does ServerCentral use my information?**

We collect, retain, and use your personally identifiable information for legitimate business purposes only, including without limitation the following: to respond to an inquiry from you or provide a quote in response to a request submitted by you (including contacting you directly to request additional information to process your inquiry or request); to contact you and to provide you information regarding ServerCentral and/or our products and services; to operate or improve the Site; to inform you of developments in our company or about products or services we believe may be of interest to you; to monitor Site visitor traffic patterns and Site usage; to comply with applicable laws, regulations and rules, and requests of relevant law enforcement and/or other governmental agencies; to enforce our Acceptable Use Policy; and/or to protect the rights, property, or safety of ServerCentral, our users, and others.

**Will ServerCentral disclose the information it collects to outside third parties?**

ServerCentral will not sell or rent the personal information we collect to third parties for any purpose, including direct or indirect mass e-mail marketing. **ServerCentral may disclose your personal information and/or IP address only to our affiliates and service providers or as otherwise described herein.** In addition, we will disclose information we maintain, including personally identifiable information when required to do so by law, or may disclose such information in response to a request from a law enforcement agency or authority. Further, we will disclose your personal information if we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

1\. Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ServerCentral;

2\. Protect and defend the rights or property of ServerCentral, the Site, or visitors to the ServerCentral Site; and

3\. Identify persons who may be violating the law, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the ServerCentral Site.

**How can I opt out of receiving communications from ServerCentral?**

You may opt out of receiving materials or other communications from us by contacting us via e-mail at [privacy@servercentral.com](mailto:privacy@servercentral.com).

**What is ServerCentral’s policy regarding children?**

We do not permit children under 13 years of age to use the Site,and we do not knowingly collect information from children. By using the Site, you represent that you are over 13 years of age.

**What safeguards are in place?**

Because security is important to both ServerCentral and you, we use commercially reasonable efforts to help ensure the security of our systems against such risks as unauthorized access, use, collection, disclosure or disposal. Reasonable security measures have been integrated into the design, implementation and day-to-day operating practices as part of ServerCentral’s commitment to protect the personal information it holds. Please be aware, however, that Internet data transmission is not always secure and we cannot warrant that information you transmit utilizing the Site is secure.

**What else should I know about my privacy when online?**

The Site contains many hyperlinks to third party Web sites. ServerCentral is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party Web sites or advertisers. ServerCentral does not share any of the individual personal information you provide ServerCentral with the third parties to which ServerCentral links. Please review the privacy policies posted on those Web sites to determine how they will collect, use and maintain your personally identifiable information. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, for example, through e-mail or discussion lists, that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from third parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you’re online.

**What if ServerCentral sells its business?**

ServerCentral may, in the future, sell or otherwise transfer some or all of its assets to a third party. The personally identifiable information and/or technical information we obtain from you via the Site may be disclosed to any potential or actual third party purchasers of such assets and/or may be among those assets transferred. In this case, we will require any such third party to agree to treat PII (as defined below) in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**How does ServerCentral assure compliance with this Privacy Policy and the Principles?**

ServerCentral uses a self-assessment approach to ensure compliance with this Privacy Policy and periodically verifies that the policy is accurate, comprehensive for the information intended to be covered, prominently displayed, completely implemented and accessible and in conformity with the Principles. We encourage interested persons to raise any concerns using the contact information provided and we will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding the user and disclosure of PII in accordance with the Principles.

If a complaint or dispute cannot be resolved through our internal process, we agree to dispute resolution using the European Data Protection Authorities, administered by the US Council of International Business, as a third party resolution provider.

**Consent To This Agreement**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the ServerCentral Terms of Use.

**Terms of Use**

By using the Site and voluntarily providing your PII to ServerCentral, you consent to the collection and use of such PII by ServerCentral as specified above. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with any information and do not use the Site.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 17, 2014. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances it is disclosed. Any modified Privacy Policy will be effective upon posting. In the event we modify this Privacy Policy, your continued use of the Site will signify your acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy.

**Contact Information**

Questions, comments, or complaints regarding the Company’s Privacy Policy, Safe Harbor Policy, or data collection and processing practices can be mailed or emailed to:

ServerCentral, Inc.  
Attn: Legal Department  
111 W. Jackson Blvd. Ste. 1600  
Chicago, IL 60604  
United States of America

_Updated on February 17, 2014_
